khojguru.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Khojguru

This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage ("Transactions"), and data gathered, on the KHOJGURU.COM web site (the "Site") and does not apply to any other web site or offline point of contact between KHOJGURU.COM or any other company, and consumers.

## COMMITMENT TO RESPECT & PROTECT CUSTOMER’S PRIVACY

KHOJGURU respects, protects & takes steps to protect & safeguard the complete privacy of our customers. We strive to take all care possible of the information that is received from you.

## SCOPE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY

It addresses the privacy extended to the visitors of KHOJGURU.COM & also identifies the type of data & information , we collect from visitors, how we disclose and use it & the steps we take to protect the privacy.

## WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT & USE IT

We don’t collect personal information from you when you visit our site unless you intend to advertise or use our services or want to know more about them. We may however, track the non – personal information about your visit which may include your domain name, webpage or complete URL from which you entered our sites, your IP address & how much time you spend on our pages etc. In order to operate the Site and provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you, we may collect profile information (i.e. information that could be used to contact you such as full name, postal address, phone number and email address), financial information (e.g. passwords and credit card numbers), demographic information (e.g. zip code, hometown, gender, purchase history information and age), public information such as user ratings and reviews and a user name from you.

## COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES

We may use cookies to tailor and improve the content we deliver to you while you are on our sites. The cookies do not contain or capture any personal information. You can configure your computer's browser to alert you when a site is attempting to send you a cookie and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. Your decision to refuse cookies from KHOJGURU.COM will not prevent you from using our sites, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of our advanced features.

## THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS AND EXTERNAL LINKS

We may accept advertisements from third-party advertisers or provide links to external Web sites. Please check the privacy policy of these advertisers and sites for information regarding their collection of information and use of cookies. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other Web sites. Any third party cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the company placing them. 

## ADVANCED TECHNOLOGY 

We may use / be using advanced technology features like codes and / or web beacons on some of our webpages to monitor the activity on our websites. Again, no personal information is captured through it.

## CHILDREN

KHOJGURU is wholly committed to protecting the privacy of the young. Our site is not designed to attract children under the age of 12 and KHOJGURU.COM does not knowingly collect personal information from children on our web sites. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 12. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

## INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE TO THIRD PARTIES

We may use aggregated information like how visitors use our Web sites and share such information with third parties in order to improve our Web sites and to help us attract advertisers and listings. For example, we may share how many individuals visited our Web site and, on average how long they stayed on each page. Such use and sharing of aggregated information will not reveal any of your personal information to third parties. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of KHOJGURU’s or such KHOJGURU Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. KHOJGURU.COM will disclose personal information, to the extent it possesses any, when in its good faith judgment the law requires it to do so, such as in response to court orders or other legal process, or when disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or the rights of our advertisers.

## SECURITY 

No transmissions over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any firewalls or secure server software we may employ. By using this Web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. KHOJGURU.COM may post a notice on our Web site if a security breach occurs.

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Our Privacy Policy is regularly reviewed and revised to make sure we continue to serve the best interests of our customers. We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Policy, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If the change would cause us to use or disclose personal information in a manner that is materially less restrictive from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify Web visitors prior to implementing the change. 

## INFORMATION OTHER WEB SITES COLLECT FROM YOU 

On the Site, we place links to other web sites operated by other parties. Some of these other web sites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other web sites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other web sites or these other web sites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other web sites. Consequently, the operators of these other web sites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the Site. We may not be held responsible for any such listing.

## OUR SECURITY PRECAUTIONS, LOCATION OF INFORMATION

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and the countries in which these computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in your country.

## TELL-A-FRIEND

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our services/site, we ask you for your friend's name and email address. KHOJGURU.COM will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the KHOJGURU.COM Site. 

## LEGAL NOTICE

KHOJGURU.COM makes no representations or warranties that any information or content provided herein is accurate, complete, or authentic; and KHOJGURU.COM shall have no liability whatsoever for information or content provided by third parties. KHOJGURU.COM reserves the right to modify any information, content or services at any time without notice.

## HELP US TO ENSURE WE HOLD ACCURATE INFORMATION 

KHOJGURU takes all reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent on the information you provide. That's why we recommend that you: * let us know if there are any errors in your personal information; and * keep us up to date with changes to personal information such as your name or address.

## HOW TO CONTACT US
